ranjish.com 2019-05-04

# Privacy Policy

**Privacy Policy for www.ranjish.com**

Last updated : September 15, 2018

If you require any more information or have any questions about our privacy policy, please feel free to contact us by email at ranjishcom [at] yahoo.com.

At www.ranjish.com, the privacy of our visitors is of extreme importance to us. This privacy policy document outlines the types of personal information is received and collected by www.ranjish.com and how it is used.

**Log Files**  
Like many other Web sites, www.ranjish.com makes use of log files. The information inside the log files includes internet protocol ( IP ) addresses, type of browser, Internet Service Provider ( ISP ), date/time stamp, referring/exit pages, and number of clicks to analyze trends, administer the site, track user?s movement around the site, and gather demographic information. IP addresses, and other such information are not linked to any information that is personally identifiable.

**Cookies and Web Beacons**  
www.ranjish.com does use cookies to store information about visitors preferences, record user-specific information on which pages the user access or visit, customize Web page content based on visitors browser type or other information that the visitor sends via their browser.

**DoubleClick DART Cookie**  
.:: Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on www.ranjish.com.  
.:: Google’s use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to users based on their visit to www.ranjish.com and other sites on the Internet.  
.:: Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy at the following URL – http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html

These third-party ad servers or ad networks use technology to the advertisements and links that appear on www.ranjish.com send directly to your browsers. They automatically receive your IP address when this occurs. Other technologies ( such as cookies, JavaScript, or Web Beacons ) may also be used by the third-party ad networks to measure the effectiveness of their advertisements and / or to personalize the advertising content that you see.

www.ranjish.com has no access to or control over these cookies that are used by third-party advertisers.

**Soundcloud Cookie**  
We use Soundcloud as our audio host. when you hear our audio poems, Soundcloud starts serving their cookies. They serve cookies and we have no control over their cookies.

If you wish to disable cookies, you may do so through your individual browser options. More detailed information about cookie management with specific web browsers can be found at the browsers’ respective websites.

**User Data (email, names, messages):  **

We promise that you will never have to worry about the email you sent us including your details, such as your email adress, your name and your phone number. Your personal data is only used by us (Ranjish.com) to get in touch with you ( Only if you desire). We never share your data with anyone.

**Content :  **

Ranjish.com is a poetry website. We are always willing to put only the unique content on our website. However this is a sharing website and everyone submits there own poetrys, so please bear with us if you find duplicate content on our website. We request you to please inform us about content you have seen on some other website too, so we can remove it from our website or get it removed from that other website.

Some users have accused us that we have shared their email address with other people. Let us assure you that we would rather choose to die then deciding to share your details with someone else. This website itself is about Trust and Love, so we would never break your trust.

**Sending Messages :**

We collect public information of a user who sends SMS from this website. We may share it with the security agencies who are investigating inappropriate messages sent from our website.
  *[Log]: people
  *[log]: people
  *[see]: sew
  *[do]: two
